{
	"xp": [
		{
			"question": "What area can you find a Werewolf <:werewolf:813589522993643530>? \n**1:** Area 1 \n**2:** Area 2 \n**3:** Area 3 \n**4:** Area 4",
			"answers": "2"
		},
		{
			"question": "What area can you find a Blue Jelly <:jelly:810738535740080128>? \n**1:** Area 1 \n**2:** Area 2 \n**3:** Area 3 \n**4:** Area 4",
			"answers": "1"
		},
		{
			"question": "In what area can you first find <:tinOre:813572436598587402>? \n**1:** Area 1 \n**2:** Area 2 \n**3:** Area 3 \n**4:** Area 4",
			"answers": "2"
		},
		{
			"question": "What is the name of the first sword you can make?",
			"answers": ["basic sword", "basicsword", "basic"]
		},
		{
			"question": "What item is this? <:log:806232602703822899> \n**1:** Maple Log \n**2:** Wooden Log \n**3:** Stick \n**4:** Log",
			"answers": "4"
		},
		{
			"question": "Is this an enemy you encounter in a battle? <:wasp:805520776311865465>? **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["yes", "y", "ye"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Is this an enemy you encounter in a battle? <:vampireEro:813496473446514728>? **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["yes", "y", "ye"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Is this an enemy you encounter in a battle? <a:eyeEro:813898212817240115> **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["no", "n"]
		},		
		{
			"question": "How much extra hp does this give you? <:hpboostB:812093133856702464>",
			"answers": "10"
		},
		{
			"question": "What was the type of enemy fought in boss 0? (The Tutorial)",
			"answers": ["bear", "brown bear", "brownbear"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Are you able to mine in area 0? **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["no", "n"]
		},
		{
			"question": "What area is the earlier you can craft a <:bronzeAxe:813572251587837953> on your own? \n**1:** Area 1 \n**2:** Area 2 \n**3:** Area 3 \n**4:** Area 4",
			"answers": "2"
		},
		{
			"question": "What area is the earlier you can craft a <:copperplatedleatherarmor:812498329371803650> on your own? \n**1:** Area 1 \n**2:** Area 2 \n**3:** Area 3 \n**4:** Area 4",
			"answers": "1"
		}
		
	],
	"gathering": [
		{
			"question": "randomLogs",
			"items": ["<:stick:801885407129370625>", "<:log:806232602703822899>", "<:mahoganylog:813650064215506954>", "<:pinelog:811035395319267348>"]
		},
		{
			"question": "randomOre",
			"items": ["<:pebble:801895841178451998>", "<:stone:801902761335586848>", "<:coppperore:810927764411646002>", "<:tinOre:813572436598587402>"]
		},
		{
			"question": "randomIngots",
			"items": ["<:copperingot:811659792447832104>", "<:bronzeIngot:813572436091994164>"]
		},
		{
			"question": "randomLetter",
			"items": [["Copper Ingot", "<:copperingot:811659792447832104>"], ["Bronze Ingot", "<:bronzeIngot:813572436091994164>"], ["Mahogany Log", "<:mahoganylog:813650064215506954>"], ["Tin Ore", "<:tinOre:813572436598587402>"], ["Stick", "<:stick:801885407129370625>"]]
		}
	],
	"artisan": [
		{
			"question": "How much extra attack does this give you? <:attackboostA:812093131826659348> ",
			"answers": "1"
		},
		{
			"question": "How much extra defence does this give you? <:defenceboostB:812093132128649247>",
			"answers": "2"
		},
		{
			"question": "Is leather required to make a <:pineshield:811813315701374996>?  **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["yes", "y", "ye"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Are sticks required to make a <:pineshield:811813315701374996>?  **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["no", "n"]
		},
		{
			"question": "Is leather required to make a <:basicshield:803356283188150324>? **yes** or **no**",
			"answers": ["no", "n"]
		}
	]
}